[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Naughty out of hurdle, maybe, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vanessa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What should I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "If I were you, I'd be doing what you know is right and nothing less in that process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "This is an extraordinary development after so long, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Completely extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "I mean this could have been pretty scandalous, isn't it, that this man, if he is the guy that did this, has been allowed to roam the streets for 33 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Scandalous, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "How does the family feel about the potential for George Zimmerman being released on bail tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, we feel that some crimes are nonbondable offense and second-degree murder is one of these, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Sybrina Fulton"]}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Tell me why, and also tell me is it a possibility this meeting could happen in the future do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, Piers, let me first say that Sybrina Fulton is a Christian woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "How are they feeling about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, obviously it's going to be very emotional being in the same room with the killer of your child.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What do you think that means for the possibility of George Zimmerman being released on bail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "In some ways, this is the perfect judge, if you're a defense lawyer, to have make this decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Is it likely, do you think, all things considered he'll be released?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I -- all things considered, I think it is likely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Well, I'm just asking, I mean, does that come into play as a factor in such a high-profile case, that not that he's a threat to other people but that his own life might be actually at risk and he's better off actually being inside, not on bail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "It's -- I've never seen a published case that argues that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "In their effort to keep him inside, can we expect new evidence to emerge by the prosecution tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Is it more difficult to get a conviction under the second-degree murder charge he's on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "It's a great question, because I think, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "It's a fascinating case, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "It really is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What do they need from somebody like you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, they all have something different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "When that specific thing is happening, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "It's not a say, it's putting him back in state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "I mean despite all these incredible things that you've experienced, to have the president of your country call you in his great hour of need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, you know, if you're thinking about yourself in a moment like that, you can't really serve, so then it would be all about you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Do you personally ever have crushing moments of self- doubt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Self-doubt as often as you do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Now be honest, when you first heard that, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "That was pretty horrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "How helpful is that to exuding the kinds of inner self-belief that you clearly have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, clearly it's not just about inner self-belief, it's really about people getting to the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Did she ever tell you she loved you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Sounds like perfect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What does he need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I'm a strategist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "In one minute or two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What's the last one of your five points?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "It's the health side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What are you thinking when it all started erupting like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Well, there was a large part that was fantastic and positive and overwhelming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Do you feel that you achieved that goal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yeah, partly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Do you think you would have had the platform to realize your dreams?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "You weren't quite what your teachers thought, were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "You have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "That was a great part, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I loved Whilemina.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Stuff you dream of, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Wearing fabulous clothing and bossing people around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "So I know that that, in the end, is the glue, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "How many times did you say you've been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Oh, boy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "You married two of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Or am I making an assumption there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Well, I do mention in the book that the two marriages that I -- I ended up getting married to I was pregnant both times that I got married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Have you matured fully or are you still slightly naughty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I have nothing going on in my life right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "If I could find for you now the perfect man, based on all you've learned about love, romance, divorce, heartbreak, what would he be like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Available, and available for a relationship, and not afraid of a relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]